MOHAMAD AMIRUL HAKIM BIN JOHARI

Jementah, Johor · +60-1136789317 · amirulhakim5383@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/amirul-hakim-0b1b9b237

An undergraduate student with a Bachelor`s degree in Web Application, I am a dedicated and detail-oriented Frontend Developer with experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and React. Experienced in problem-solving and analytical skills in project development. Passionate in designing visually appealing and user-friendly web applications in order to make a valuable website.

EDUCATION

Universiti Tun Hussien Onn, Johor, Malaysia

1 2020-2023

Bachelor of Computer Science (Web Technology) with Honours

- Current CGPA: 3.53
- Awards: Dean List for Semester 1 (GPA:3.67), Semester 4 (GPA: 3.54), and Semester 5 (GPA: 3.70)

Universiti Tun Hussien Onn, Johor, Malaysia

2018-2020

Diploma in Information Technology

- CGPA: 3.31
- Awards: Dean List for Semester 3 (GPA: 3.51)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Century Bond Bhd, Kulai, Johor

JANUARY 2020 - APRIL 2020

IT Assistant (Contract)

- Migrating data from the Dos system to Syspro using a parallel migration approach.
- Observed data entry from every department into new applications for each module such as the purchase module, sales module, and production module.
- Collaborated with the production department, including graphic design and QA testers to adapt to the new system named Syspro in the migration process.
- Observe and understand the data flow in the backend of the new application in MySQL.
- Ensure that the internet has a satisfactory speed by ensuring that each computer has a network, whether that computer uses Ethernet or Wi-Fi to avoid network problems on the server.
- Produced and updated the IT Compliance for the IT department to ensure standards and regulations were met.

Century Bond Bhd, Kulai, Johor

SEPTEMBER 2019 - JANUARY 2020

IT Assistant (Intern)

- Observed the product flow from pre-production to post-production in packaging products such as paper bags and boxes.
- Checked the quality of IT equipment such as monitors, printers, hard disks, and others to keep organizational equipment in good working condition.
- Maintained the server room to ensure all network devices and servers were clean, and wellventilated with an unobstructed airflow, and all loose cables were clearly labeled and stored correctly.

SKILLS & OTHER

Computer Skills:

 CSS, JavaScript, React, HTML and XML, PHP, Nodejs, ASP.NET, Microsoft Azure, Database management software, MySQL, Figma, Flutter

Language Skills:

- Bahasa Melayu: Advanced
- English: Intermediate

MINI PROJECT

FootCourse:

- Football module website that provides multiple modules and many features such as football boots comparison and testing your skill in football.
- Build in JavaScript, Html, ReactJS, NodeJS and Tailwind CSS

Gadzilla:

- The website that sells gadgets as an e-commerce website.
- Build with JavaScript, Html, and CSS.

Login and Signup with Security Implementation:

- Login and Sign Up built-in with the hashing method and SQL injection protection.
- Build with JavaScript, Html, CSS, and PHP.

Web of Thing:

- A WordPress blog about web technology with content syndicate and improved SEO.
- Build with WordPress.

Photography System Management:

- A photography management system that manages employee and client appointments for photo session.
- Build with MySQL, Asp.Net, CSS and Html.

CO-CURRICULAR

Participation:

- Managed to be selected in the football team to represent the Faculty of Computer Science and Information Technology on SAF (Sukan Antara Fakulti).
- Represented the UTHM Dragon Boat Team in several tournaments.

REFERENCES

Puan Hayanti Binti Hafit

Position: Lecturer and Final Project Supervisor

Email: hana@uthm.edu.my Contact No: 013-7795597